proxy-service.de 2012-10-14

# Privacy Policy

Our service may collect information about you during your visit. This document describes the information we collect and how it is used. Proxy-Service.de may share aggregate information about our Users with advertisers, business partners, sponsors and other third parties. We use aggregate information to customize our content and advertising to deliver services that are well tailored to our users needs. 

**Security of Information**

The security of our users' personally identifiable information is an important priority. We exercise great care in providing secure transmission of your information from your PC to our servers. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or through our Services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on and through our systems. Our Site is secure to the best of our abilities. We use our best efforts to keep our Site safe from unauthorized access, and to minimize the number of people who have access to sensitive information. We cannot absolutely guarantee the security of our Site, and will not be responsible for breaches of security. 

**Server Access Logs**

Our server logs all requests. The data recorded includes information provided by your browser (user agent and referring page) as well as the requested URI, the time and date and your IP address. The data recorded in these logs may be used for detecting and preventing abuse. We may also collate this data for statistical purposes.

**Service Logs**

The service provided on this website allows access to external, third-party websites. We may record your IP address and the websites you visit. The logs are used primarily for monitoring requests and ensuring no illegal activity is undertaken. Any violations of our terms of use may result in disclosure of the data recorded in our logs to an appropriate third party, which may include your Internet Service Provider (ISP) or local authorities. We may also be required, by law, to provide logs of our service and if requested, such data will be disclosed. We may also use service logs for stastical purposes.

**Cookies**

Our website stores a cookie on your computer, if allowed by your browser's privacy settings *. The cookie used by our service uniquely identifies you to the server and allows our website to remember your preferences.

We may also use third-party advertising partners on our website. Advertisers may send you cookies or use web beacons. We have no control over cookies, web beacons or the information collected by our advertisers. Consult the third-party advertiser's privacy policy for more information on their practices.

The service we provide may attempt to forward third-party cookies from the websites you choose to browse. We have no control over indirect cookies and you are advised to consult the privacy policy of the applicable third-party website. If you do not wish to receive any such indirect cookies, please disable the "Allow Cookies" option.

* For more information on configuring your browser, see www.aboutcookies.org or the documentation for your browser. We are not responsible for the content of any third-party websites.

**Policy Modifications**

We reserve the right to review and change this Policy for this Site and/or any other rules and policies relating to the Site at any time and to provide notification solely by posting an updated version on the Site.

  * Proxy \- 
  * Edit Browser Agent \- 
  * Manage Cookies
  * Privacy \- 
  * Our Terms \- 
  * Impressum

Pink oranges turn blue when u eat a chicken 4 morning tea.  
Your orange skins find this offensive!
